http://www.coalvillesc.org.uk/privacy-policy.php/

Please select:« Return to pageHomeLatest newsAbout usAbout usCommittee/coachesClub ConstitutionLiability Insurance Document Swim 21WelfareCodes of ConductData ProtectionEquity PolicySafeguarding PolicyWelfare contactJoining the ClubJoining & TrialsSubscriptions and FeesTraining informationPool locationsFixturesCalendarAnnual Club Championship RecordsVolunteersUseful Swimming InfoASA Speed AwardsNational Qualifying Times - 2015Personal Best (PB) recordsSwimming LessonsLong course PBsDiddy Team SwimmersDisqualification informationPool locationsLASACATsNutritional InformationGalas and Open meetsCounties Consideration Times 2019Counties Qualification Times 2020East Midland Qualifying Times - 2019Improve performanceSwimmer Development - City of Leicester ProgressionVolunteersContact
The home of competitive swimming in North West Leicestershire
Latest news
Merch
Read more >
HomeLatest newsAbout usAbout usCommittee/coachesClub ConstitutionLiability Insurance Document Swim 21WelfareCodes of ConductData ProtectionEquity PolicySafeguarding PolicyWelfare contactJoining the ClubJoining & TrialsSubscriptions and FeesTraining informationPool locationsFixturesCalendarAnnual Club Championship RecordsVolunteersUseful Swimming InfoASA Speed AwardsNational Qualifying Times - 2015Personal Best (PB) recordsSwimming LessonsLong course PBsDiddy Team SwimmersDisqualification informationPool locationsLASACATsNutritional InformationGalas and Open meetsCounties Consideration Times 2019Counties Qualification Times 2020East Midland Qualifying Times - 2019Improve performanceSwimmer Development - City of Leicester ProgressionVolunteersContact
Privacy Policy & Cookies
This privacy policy sets out how Coalville Swimming Club uses and protects any information that you
give Coalville Swimming Club when you use this website.
Coalville Swimming Club is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to
provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured
that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Coalville Swimming Club may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check
this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1st
July 2013.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name and job title
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in
particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other
information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may
contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according
to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or
disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to
safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
We sometimes place small data files on your computer. These are known as cookies. Most websites do this.
They improve things by:
remembering settings, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you visit a new page
measuring how you use the website so we can make sure it meets your needs
These cookies aren’t used to identify you personally. They’re just here to make the site work better for you.
Indeed, you can manage and/or delete these small files as you wish. We do not store any personal information
in the cookies - nor do we place any cookies relating to advertising on the website.
To learn more about cookies and how to manage them, visit
AboutCookies.org. Or please read on to find out
more about how and where we use cookies.
Measuring website usage (Google Analytics)
We use Google Analytics to collect information about how people use this site. We do
this to make sure it’s meeting its users’ needs and to understand how we could do it better.
Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got
here and what you click on. We do not collect or store your personal information (e.g. your name or
address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are. We do not allow Google to use or
share our analytics data with third parties.
You
can get more information on the cookies that Google Analytics stores in your browser at this
link.
Highlighting menus and logging onto the website
If you log into this website (to administer the content, comment on a blog, carry out
a purchase etc) then we store any details that we need to on our server. To link your "session"
data on our server with your browser session a small cookie is placed in your browser - containing an
anonymised link to the session. As soon as you close your broswer this session cookie is deleted.
Remembering whether you've seen the school pop-up alerts
When we alert you to an important issue (school closed due to snow etc) - we don't want that alert
popping up on EVERY page you visit. It would be annoying! So we check that you've seen it once and then
store a cookie - so you only see it once per browsing session.
We determine that both these types of cookies are essential to the running of the
website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to
leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we
cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting
such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look
at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate
that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you
may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at
info@coalvillesc.org.uk
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your
permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional
information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to
happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A
small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write
to Coalville Swimming Club via our contact page.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or
email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be
incorrect.
Calendar 2020Regional championship qualifying times 2020Disqualification InformationCounties Qualification Times 2020Annual Club Championship RecordsWhere and when we train
Sorry. You need to upgrade your browser
You are using Internet Explorer 8
This is considered an out of date browser. This website has been developed with modern browsers in mind to allow it to display at its best in a wide variety of viewing situations - including mobile viewing. But we haven't supported older browsers like IE8. Please upgrade to the latest version of Internet Explorer - or try Mozilla Firefox or Google Chrome. Both are excellent browsers.
Thank you.
© 2013 - 2020 Coalville Swimming Club. All rights reserved.Home   Site map   Privacy Policy & Cookies   Admin
Swimming club website design byPeter Bourne Communications
